[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
Dammit.
How come that catwalk
doesn't have any supports?
The last one had dangling
cables after it collapsed.
If I had one of those, I could
swing
across to the other side like
Tarzan.
That would be dope.
They did that in Star Wars, too.
Dude swinging across a gap with
some babe holding onto him.
That was a grappling hook,
though.
That's what this suit needs:
a grappling hook.
Then I could swing my way to
victory
instead of performing this
balancing act.
Bugs can crawl on walls.
Maybe I should've been a bug.
Go Team Kafka!
I'd at least want four arms
like the god Shiva.
Okay, now I have some options.
I can either fall to my
death in this black pit,
land on the edge and gore myself
on the jagged metal mesh,
or land on the concrete and
maybe break my legs.
And before, all I had was the
pit.
Jee-heez!
I'm going to have arthritis by
the time I'm 30 at this rate.
Assuming I even live that long.
Ah, who am I kidding?
I've got a gun.
Oh, what the hell?
Another catwalk is out?
And what is THAT?
It's got tentacles for a face.
It's a Cthulhu dog.
Well, it's attacking the
face-huggers;
it can't be all bad.
I'll just wait until it's
done with them and--
[coughing]
Plegh!  Tastes like
dead caterpillars!  Pleh!
Okay, squid-head.
Say hello to Yog-Sothoth
and the Elder Gods for me!
Hey, a rope!
Now I can be Tarzan!
[Tarzan yell]
Hey, wait, that's not a rope.
That's a...these are like...
jellyfish or something.
If I swung on that, it could
come crashing down on me.
These aliens are just good for
nothing.
These crates are good for
something.
This one just broke my fall.
That means aliens are
worth less than crates.
Which is, what, a few bucks?
Well, at least I got to rinse my
mouth out.
What I really need is some
toothpaste,
but now it tastes a little
bit less like squid snot.
If that water's toxic, too, then
at
least the toxins are tasteless.
I'll have time to worry about
mouth cancer later.
Hey, wait.
What's up with this ceiling?
That looks like a ceiling
designed to
have moving walls that crush
people.
Well, there's no bloodstains.
Oh, God.  That was a pun.
"What's up with this ceiling?"
What's wrong with me?
I'd punch somebody in the
mouth if they said that to me.
Huh.  Wow....
I wasn't expecting this.
This... this must be our
box-smashing room.
I mean, what, we have a
bottomless pit,
and the sides are all plate
metal that look
strong enough to withstand a
missile blast.
This room must've cost a couple
hundred thousand to build.
Eat your heart out, taxpayers.
This is where your money goes.
I mean, we get most of our money
from the Department of Defense,
and this is what
we're spending it on.
And here, I thought my
division was wasting money.
We were doing a hell of a lot
more than smashing boxes.
This whole company's just
retarded.
Ugh, there's no door up here.
Is there really no way around
this?
What do the workers normally do?
Just ride the crates down
like it's a ski-lift?
Well...
Okay, extreme hopscotch!
Let's do this!
No room for error here.
It kind of reminds me of that
cooking
show I saw filmed in the
Philippines,
where two chefs would compete
against
each other to make the best
dish,
and, at the end, they would cut
the loser's head off with a
sword.
I think the show got cancelled.
Well, now I have an answer if
anyone ever
asks me what the dumbest thing
I've ever did was.
I can say-WHOA!
"There was this one time I was
jumping
across these crates suspended
above
"a bottomless pit, even though
I didn't really know where I was
going.
"Or-or-or, there was the time
I crawled into a drainage pipe,
"opened up the floodgate
and almost drowned.
"I shouldn't even be alive,
really."
Ahh, made it.
So, where do these things go
that we need so many crates?
That doesn't go anywhere.
That's a wall.
That....
That means we're just loading up
crates
so we can drop them over that
pit.
That means that there's no
damned point to this whole room.
This whole place is such a wash.
Good ol' New Mexico.  We're
really
making a name for the state.
First, they invented the
atomic bomb in Los Alamos.
Now, we've invented mean-ass
aliens
that teleport out of nowhere.
I'm not sure which is worse.
You know, when they
invented the atomic bomb,
they were afraid it was going to
catch the atmosphere on fire
and burn up the whole earth, but
they did it anyway.
That took balls.
Not us, though.
The only people taking the risks
were the ones that didn't
understand them in the first
place.
We're not brave.
We're just stupid.
Well, I'm on the other side.
So, that's what?
Three-for-three?
Man, we've picked the wrong
contractor to build these
catwalks.
El Sleazo's Discount
Construction.
Bribing building inspectors for
over 40 years.
YES!
Time to get the hell out of
here.
I hate elevator music.